Amit Yadav

Mumbai, Maharashtra, India

Lead Systems Engineer with 8 years of experience deploying solutions, handling live environments, developing robust code and focusing on automation and maintenance. I work extensively with Google Cloud Platform, Kubernetes, Helm, Terraform, etc.

amityadavk2@gmail.com in linkedin.com/in/amit-k-yadav/

stackoverflow.com/users/10003710/amit-yadav

+91 8655120760

🕠 github.com/amit-k-yadav

medium.com/@amityadavk2

WORK EXPERIENCE

Lead Systems Engineer EPAM Systems

06/2022 - Present

Senior DevOps Engineer Ignite Solutions

06/2018 - 06/2022

System Software Engineer Infosys Ltd.

11/2016 - 05/2018

PROJECTS

- Banking Client | DevOps | EPAM Systems GoogleCloudPlatform, GitHub Actions ,Kubernetes, Terraform, Helm, Git-crypt, Docker, Python, Nginx, Apache, BigQuery
- Machine Cover | Backend, DevOps | Ignite Solutions Ansible, Python, RabbitMQ, MongoDB
- ° CUDDLY | Full Stack, DevOps | Ignite Solutions Ansible CakePHP, Angular, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, MySQL
- Restaurant Finder | Backend | Infosys Ltd. Python, Django REST Framework, MySQL

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Engineering

Atharva College of Engineering - Mumbai

08/2012 - 06/2016 7.98 CGPA

HSC

BhawaniShankar College - Mumbai

2010 - 2012 85.33 %

SSC

Khernagar High School - Mumbai

2009 - 2010 85.27 %

TECHNICAL SKILLS

DevOps:

Google Cloud Platform, Kubernetes, Helm, Terraform, Ansible, Jenkins, Kafka, Docker, Nginx, Apache, Apigee, KeyCloak, AWS SES, AWS Lambda, SonarQube

Languages / Frameworks / libraries:

Python, Django, DRF, Flask, CakePHP, JavaScript, JQuery, Shell Script, React

Databases / Data Warehouses:

MySQL, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, DynamoDB, BigQuery

BLOGS

TCP services Load balancer for multiple Kubernetes Clusters [link]

Deploy Kafka-connect on Kubernetes using Helm [link]

ACHIEVEMENTS

Open source contribution to Confluent's cp-helm-charts [link]

Maintaining an active StackOverflow profile with 3400+ reputation and a reach of 3+ lac users [link]

Reported an issue that got acknowledged and fixed by Google [link]

LANGUAGES

Enalish

Hindi

Full Professional Proficiency Full Professional Proficiency

INTERESTS

Blogging Guitar / Music Trekking